<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>







    <string name="pythonpro_text">

        Python is a powerful multi-purpose programming language created by Guido van Rossum.\n

        It has simple easy-to-use syntax, making it the perfect language\n
        for someone trying to
        learn computer programming for the first time.\n

        This is a comprehensive guide on how to get started in Python,\n
        why you should learn it and how you can learn it.\n

        However, if you have knowledge of other programming languages\n
        and want to quickly get started with Python, visit Python tutorial page.\n</string>


    <string name="javascriptpro_text">

        By itself, HTML doesn’t have any smarts: It can’t do math,\n
        it can’t figure out if someone has correctly\n
        filled out a form, and it can’t make decisions based\n
        on how a web visitor interacts with it.\n
        Basically, HTML lets people read text, look at pictures, watch videos,\n
        and click links to move to other web pages with more text, pictures,\n
        and videos. In order to add intelligence to your web pages so they can\n
        respond to your site’s visitors, you need JavaScript.\n

        JavaScript lets a web page react intelligently.\n
        With it, you can create smart web forms that let visitors know\n
        when they’ve forgotten to include necessary information. You can make elements\n</string>



    <string name="dartpro_text">

        Dart is an open-source general-purpose programming language.\n
        It is originally developed by Google and later approved as a standard by ECMA.\n
        Dart is a new programming language meant for the server as well as the browser.\n
        Introduced by Google, the Dart SDK ships with its compiler – the Dart VM.\n
        The SDK also includes a utility -dart2js,\n
        a transpiler that generates JavaScript equivalent of a Dart Script.\n
        This tutorial provides a basic level understanding of the Dart programming language.\n

        Audience This tutorial will be quite helpful for all those developers\n
        who want to develop single-page web applications using Dart.\n
        It is meant for programmers with a strong hold on object-oriented concepts.\n

        Prerequisites The tutorial assumes that the readers have adequate exposure to\n
        object-oriented programming concepts. If you have worked on JavaScript,\n
        then it will help you further to grasp the concepts of Dart quickly.\n</string>



    <string name="fluterpro_text">

        Flutter’s Stateful Hot Reload preserves the state of your app.\n
        This design enables you to view the effect of the most recent change only,\n
        without throwing away the current state. For example,\n
        if your app requires a user to log in, you can modify\n
        and hot reload a page several levels down in the navigation hierarchy,\n
        without re-entering your login credentials. State is kept,\n
        which is usually the desired behavior.\n

        If code changes affect the state of your app (or its dependencies),\n
        the data your app has to work with might not be fully consistent\n
        with the data it would have if it executed from scratch.\n
        The result might be different behavior after hot reload versus a hot restart.\n

        For example, if you modify a class definition from extending StatelessWidget\n
        to StatefulWidget (or the reverse), after hot reload the previous state of\n
        your app is preserved.\n However, the state might not be compatible with the
        new changes.\n</string>



    <string name="phppro_text">
        The PHP Hypertext Preprocessor (PHP) is a programming language that allows web\n
        developers to create dynamic content that interacts with databases.\n
        PHP is basically used for developing web based software applications.\n
        This tutorial helps you to build your base with PHP.\n

        Why to Learn PHP?\n\n
        PHP started out as a small open source project that\n
        evolved as more and more people found out how useful it was.\n
        Rasmus Lerdorf unleashed the first version of PHP way back in 1994.\n

        PHP is a MUST for students and working professionals to become a great Software\n
        Engineer specially when they are working in Web Development Domain.\n
        I will list down some of the key advantages of learning PHP:\n

        PHP is a recursive acronym for "PHP: Hypertext Preprocessor".\n
    </string>

</resources>