<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ListViewCreator</string>


    <string-array name="programming_name">

        <item>Kotlin</item>
        <item>Java</item>
        <item>Python</item>
        <item>Fluter</item>
        <item>Dart</item>
        <item>Android</item>
        <item>Go</item>
        <item>C</item>
        <item>C#</item>
        <item>PHP</item>
        <item>Java Script</item>
        <item>Rubby</item>
        <item>SQLite</item>
        <item>My SQL</item>
        <item>Firebase</item>
        <item>Java Swipt</item>
        <item>Machine Lerning</item>
        <item>AI</item>
        <item>Laravel</item>
        <item>Janngo</item>


    </string-array>


    <!--&lt;!&ndash;This is name... &ndash;&gt;-->
    <!--<string name="java">Java</string>-->
    <!--<string name="python">Python</string>-->
    <!--<string name="javascript">Jaava Script</string>-->
    <!--<string name="dart">Dart</string>-->
    <!--<string name="fluter">Fluter</string>-->
    <!--<string name="php">PHP</string>-->
    <!--<string name="title_text">This is a Title</string>-->
    <!--<string name="set_message">Do you want to Exit ? </string>-->


    <!--This is String file.. -->


    <string name="kotlinPro_text">
        The PHP Hypertext Preprocessor (PHP) is a programming language that allows web\n
        developers to create dynamic content that interacts with databases.\n
        PHP is basically used for developing web based software applications.\n
        This tutorial helps you to build your base with PHP.\n

        Why to Learn PHP?\n\n
        PHP started out as a small open source project that\n
        evolved as more and more people found out how useful it was.\n
        Rasmus Lerdorf unleashed the first version of PHP way back in 1994.\n

        PHP is a MUST for students and working professionals to become a great Software\n
        Engineer specially when they are working in Web Development Domain.\n
        I will list down some of the key advantages of learning PHP:\n

        PHP is a recursive acronym for "PHP: Hypertext Preprocessor".\n
    </string>


    <string name="javapro_text">

        Java is a popular general-purpose programming language and computing platform.\n
        It is fast, reliable, and secure. According to Oracle, the company that\n
        owns Java, Java runs on 3 billion devices worldwide.\n

        Considering the number of Java developers, devices running Java,\n and companies adapting
        it, its safe to say that Java will be around for many years to come.\n

        This guide will provide everything you need to know about\n
        Java programming language before you learn it. More specifically,\n
        you will learn about features of Java programming,\n
        its applications, reasons to learn it, and how you can learn it the right way.\n</string>





</resources>
